So, um...
(千夏)あのね もしかして
I think I might be in love
好きかもしれない
シロくんのこと
with you, Shiro-kun.
Episode Six
I Might Actually
Wait, seriously?
(宇佐)マジで？
｢謝っといて｣ってそんな… あッ
And you want me to apologize?
Sorry, Senpai...
先輩 すいません
親が うっかり
今月の家賃 振り込み忘れたって
My mom forgot to pay this month's rent.
(律)少々なら大丈夫だと思うよ
It's okay if you're a little late.
麻弓さんや 彩花さんも
よく遅れてるし
Mayumi-san and Sayaka-san are late all the time.
Shiro-san has never been late, though.
シロさんは
一度も遅れたことないらしいけど
ええッ意外 そういうところは
しっかりしてんだ
What? That's a shock...
So he can be responsible about that.
そういうところが
イラッとするよね
That's what makes him so irritating.
Shiro, you pig
She's related to Sumiko,
all right
Senpai can be pretty brutal sometimes.
<先輩 ときどき辛辣>
Bamboo for sale.
しかしシロさん どこから収入を？
I wonder where his income comes from...
Bamboo...
(シロ)♬～さおや～ さおだけ～
Bamboo for sale.
Oh, it's Rit-chan and Usa-kun.
…って 律ちゃんと宇佐くん
想定外の収入源 きた
That's the last income source I expected.
≪(シロ)いやいや違うよ➡
No, you've got it wrong.
住子さんの友達の竹林で
伐採の手伝いをして➡
I was helping one of Sumiko-san's friends cut down bamboo on his farm,
ちょっと もらっただけだって
and he let me have some.
じゃ 何で歌ってたんですか？
So why were you singing?
それは そういう気分で
I just happened to be in the mood.
(麻弓)竹なんて どうするんだよ
What are you going to do with all that bamboo?
Put up a wish tree for Tanabata?
七夕でもやる気か？
(彩花)や～だ
I don't want a wish tree that'll end up
そんな 短冊が｢いい男｣で
埋め尽くされそうな七夕
covered with wishes for a hot boyfriend.
竹馬で練り歩いてたら
小学生あたりに大受けだよ
If I put together stilts to walk around on,
I bet the grade school kids will love it.
そんなことしたら
また通報されますよ
If you do that, they'll call the cops on you again.
心外だな 小学生に興味ないよ
そのお母さんにはあるけど
That's just harsh! I'm not interested in grade school kids!
I'm interested in their mothers, though!
心外と言うほど 外れてないっすよ
That's not really any better.
(住子)シロくん 警察署から電話よ
Shiro-kun!
You have a call from the police!
逮捕か
ええッ 電話で連絡来るの!?➡
Arrested, huh?
What? They arrest you over the phone?
ええ ああ はい はい
Yes. Uh, yes.
Yes.
この前 散歩中に財布拾ってさ
交番に届けたんだよね
The other day, I was taking a walk when I found a wallet.
I dropped it off at the police box.
お巡りさん 驚いてたなあ
The officer was very surprised.
｢自首!?｣って顔してる
He thought you were turning yourself in!
≪(シロ)謝礼いらないと言ったら
戸惑ってたよ
He seemed confused when I said that I didn't need a reward.
｢自首は!?｣って顔してる
He was wondering why you weren't turning yourself in!
さっき 持ち主が
出てきたみたいでさ
They said the owner finally turned up.
いいことすると気分がいいねえ
へえ
It feels good when you do something nice.
お礼だけでも言いたい って
明日 こっちに来るみたい
They want to drop by tomorrow to thank me.
お財布 女物だったんでしょ？
そこからﾛﾏﾝｽが生まれたりして
It was a girl's wallet, yes?
Perhaps this will lead to romance.
That could...
そんなうまい話 あるかも
また～
actually happen.
Aw, come on...
お財布 届けてくれて
ありがとうございました
Thank you very much for turning in my wallet.
This is a token of our appreciation.
(母)これ つまらないものですが
Oh, that wasn't necessary.
そんな… よろしかったのに
娘が大切にしていた財布なので
どうしても お礼を…
My daughter was very attached to that wallet,
so we wanted to thank you.
The mother looks really uncomfortable.
お母さん めっちゃ目が泳いでる
そりゃ 相手がシロさんだし
Well, it's Shiro-san.
どう見ても
娘に近づけたくない部類だもんな
He's obviously not someone you'd want near your daughter.
でも 今 危ないのは…➡
But right now,
娘よりも お母さんだけどね
the mother is the one in danger.
Man, having an elegant mother in her 40s
avoid all eye contact with you feels amazing...
Chinatsu-chan, was it?
千夏ちゃんだっけ
プリンは好きかしら？
Do you like pudding?
私が作ったんだけど
よかったら どう？
It should be nice
and chilled now
I made some earlier. Would you like some?
いえ そんな もうおいとまして…
No, that won't be necessary. We need to get going.
千夏は残って食べます
I'm going to stay and have some.
ママは帰っていいよ 家近いし
You can go home, Mom.
It's not that far away.
≪(住子)どうぞ
Here you go.
すっごく おいしい！
It tastes so good!
すいません
この子 プリン 大好物で
I'm sorry about this. Pudding is her favorite.
お口に合って良かったわ
≪(千夏)ごちそうさまでした
I'm glad she likes it.
Thank you very much.
What are you making?
何作ってるんですか？
ピタゴラ装置っぽいの➡
Something you'd see on PythagoraSwitch.
Roll, roll, roll, roll!
ここに子供っているの？
いないよ
Are there any kids here?
Nope.
じゃあ 何のために？
やったら楽しいかな って
Why are you making that, then?
Hm? Because it'll be fun.
But you're a grown-up.
≪(千夏)大人なのに？
うんッ？
遊びは子供だけの特権じゃないよ
Kids aren't the only ones who get to have fun.
大人だって
遊ぶときは遊ぶんだから
Grown-ups like to have fun, too.
Even normal grown-ups?
普通の大人も？
もう俺 ダメな大人カテゴリ内？
I'm already considered a failure as a grown-up?
≪(千夏)組み立てないの？
≪(シロ)まず部品を作らないと
Aren't you going to put it together?
I have to make all the parts first.
≪(千夏)ええッ つまんない
What? That's no fun.
≪(シロ)家近いなら
また遊びに来てよ
If you live nearby, you can come over again.
(シロ)いつでもいいよ
(千夏)バイバイ
Drop by anytime.
Bye-bye!
I'll make pudding for you again.
またプリンも作ってあげるわね
She was pretty cute.
かわいい子でしたね
ね～ッ
Yep.
Ｓの可能性がチラ見えしてて
And she has the potential to become a sadist.
知りたくない 少女のそんな可能性
I don't want to hear you say that about a schoolgirl.
The "S" in schoolgirl stands for sadist!
<少女のＳは ＳのＳ！>
I'd like to watch her grow up,
≪(シロ)成長を
見守りたいところだけど➡
but I'm sure she has more fun playing with her friends,
友達と遊ぶ方が楽しいだろうし
もう来ないだろうね
so she probably won't be back.
But he was wrong.
ピタゴラ 完成した？
Did you finish the Pythagoras?
No, I'm not even close. It's no further along than yesterday.
いや まだ全然
昨日と変わらないよ
What? But it doesn't seem like you have anything else to do.
えッ それしか
やることなさそうなのに
何で進んでないの？
Why haven't you made any progress?
Yes! My ability to identify sadists is spot-on!
ヒュー 俺のＳ見分け力 絶好調！
でも やることないことはないよ
≪(千夏)何やってたの？
But I actually have other things to do.
What were you doing?
Uh...
え～ッ その… 小説書いたり
Well, I write novels...
すっご～い
Amazing.
scoff
おもいきり しょっぱい目と
冷笑をありがとう➡
Thank you for the scathing look and sneer!
小説の方はちょっとおいといて
ピタゴラに集中してもいいかな
Well, I guess I can stop writing and
focus on the Pythagoras for a bit.
Shouldn't grown-ups never give up?
大人が
すぐ投げ出していいの？
My teacher always tells me not to give up.
千夏のお稽古の先生は
｢諦めるな｣って うるさいよ
Yes, but sometimes, things just don't work out.
ああ でも どうしても
うまくいかないときもあるから➡
頑張りたいとき
頑張れなくなるから
You won't be able to work hard when it's really needed.
何年 頑張る力ためてるの？
So, how many years are you going to save up energy to work hard?
おおッ おおうッ
At this rate, you'll never finish the Pythagoras.
そんな調子じゃ いつまでたっても
ピタゴラ完成しなさそうだし
I'll start coming over to help you make it!
千夏が ここに通って
一緒に作ったげる
えッ 友達とか いいの？
Huh? What about your friends?
うん まあ しょうがないしね
Eh, well...
I can't do anything about that.
そのかわり すごいの作るよ
了解です！
To make up for it, we'll make a super one!
Roger that!
Shiro-kun.
シロくん
いい感じになってきたけど
フィニッシュはどうするの？
It's coming along well,
but what's the finish going to look like?
I'd like to do something flashy.
できれば 派手にしたいよね～
She's been coming over every day.
毎日来てんな あの子
シロさんに なついちゃったみたい
Looks like she's grown attached to Shiro-san.
いつの間にか 立派なのが出来たし
That looks pretty impressive all of a sudden.
I have an idea.
≪(千夏)考えたんだけど➡
大きめのハンマーを仕掛けて
We can set up a giant hammer
装置自体を 叩きつぶす
って どう？
that will smash the entire device.
What do you think?
そのままＳこやかに
お育ちください
Please grow up to be a sadist.
まあ 薄目で見れば ほほえましい
Well, if you squint, it's actually rather sweet.
Can't see
I guess he hasn't crossed the line yet, morally speaking.
倫理的には ギリ大丈夫か…
いいや あれは危うい
彩花さん
Well, he's cutting it close.
Sayaka-san?
恋してるっつか
I get the feeling she's in love... or more like she wants to be.
恋したがってるにおいがする
やめろよ
Don't say that!
あの子 ｼﾛのｽﾄﾗｲｸｿﾞｰﾝだから
ﾛﾘ克服しちゃうかもしれねえだろ
She falls right into his strike zone,
so he might go pedo!
Huge!
I don't want to see someone from this apartment on the news!
同じアパートのヤツが
ニュースになるのは嫌だぞ
Deviant Complex
Then people will think I'm like him.
Thank you very much.
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
で 同類って言われるんだ
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Deviant Complex
Deviant Pedo
Shirosaki, the suspect (Alias: Shiro)
Doesn't he just seem like a big brother to her?
仲いいお兄さん って感じじゃ
ないすか？
かしこそうだし
道は踏み外さなそう
She seems like a smart girl, so I don't think she'll do anything stupid.
Yeah, that's right.
But we were wrong, again.
<という予想に また反して>
あのね もしかして
So, um...
I think I might be in love
好きかもしれない
シロくんのこと
with you, Shiro-kun.
ありがとう
俺も千夏ちゃん好きだよ
Thank you.
I like you, too, Chinatsu-chan.
I hope you'll tell me that again in nine years.
９年後に 同じ言葉を聞きたいな
<良かった
ゆがみない18歳以上シールドで>
Thank goodness.
Relief
The eighteen-year-old age barrier holds strong.
I need to do something for Sumiko-san,
Relief
俺ちょっと 住子さんと
用事あるから 庭で待ってて
Relief
so wait in the yard for me.
There's still time to set her right.
今なら まだ修正きくだろう
It doesn't take much
小学生の恋愛なんて ちょっと
口出されたらコロッと変わるって
to change the mind of a girl in grade school.
Are you sure about this?
大丈夫ですか？
まッ うまく言うから任せとけ
Oh, I know just what to say, so trust me.
なあ
Hey.
A kid in grade school could never handle a freak like Shiro.
シロは 小学生には扱いきれん
変態度だぞ
将来性ないし やめとけよ なッ？
And he has no future, so don't even bother. Okay?
<デリカシー皆無！>
She's not even trying to be subtle!
ぬ 盗み聞き!?
Y-You were eavesdropping?!
Now, now. If you want to love someone, go with him.
まあまあ 好きになるなら
こっちにしとけよ
若いし これでなかなか
恥骨のある男だし
He's younger and he has a strong pelvis.
ないよ！ いや あるけど
I do not!
Er, I do, but still!
And he's still 100% unused.
すみずみまで新品だし
ウザい青春 喜んでつきあうし
He'll be happy to play along with your silly games.
好条件だろ
条件で好きになるわけじゃない
He meets all the conditions.
There are no conditions when it comes to love.
何だ こいつ
ダメ男に引っ掛かるのを
What's wrong with her?
I'm trying to save her from that failure of a guy.
止めてやってんのに
イラッとするなあ
She's really making me mad...
You're criticizing your own equal...
ああッ もう まどろっこしい！
ちょッ 麻弓さん
Man, this is too much effort!
Wait, Mayumi-san!
悪いんだけど 実はあれ
Sorry,
but he's already my boyfriend.
私の彼氏でさ ごめんな
Too bad for you.
そっちは 条件で好きになった方が
いいんじゃ… 年的に
Maybe you should be looking for someone who meets conditions,
given your age...
A little kid shouldn't be thinking about love!
小学生が色気づきやがって
ガキは ガキ仲間と
ガキガキしてりゃいいんだよ！
Kids should be kiddying it up with the other kids!
ガキガキ？
先輩 そこ？
Kiddying it up?
Senpai, that's your concern?
そんなんじゃ ハブられっぞ
バーカ
Other kids will shut you out if you're like this, idiot!
とにかく シロは私の犬なんだから
ガキの出る幕なんて ない…
Anyway, Shiro's my dog,
so a kid like you has no chance of...
泣～かした
You made her cry.
And you're three times her age...
二回りも違う子供相手に
I'm not that much older!
そこまで違わねえよ！
I couldn't bear to watch that immature display.
本気すぎて 正視できない
大人気なさ
I'm gonna tell Sumiko-san on you.
≪(彩花)住子さんに言ってやろ～
B-But...
だって あいつも
ひどいこと言ったもん！
But she was being mean to me!
I was just doing the same!
だから私も言い返しただけだもん
I didn't do anything wrong!
She's on the same level as the kid.
What happened to
千夏ちゃん どうしたんだろう？
Chinatsu-chan?
She was all excited about coming over this morning,
土曜日は朝から来るって
張り切ってたのに 来なかったな
but she never showed up.
And she left so abruptly yesterday.
昨日は急に帰っちゃったしね
プリン作ってたんだけど
I made pudding for her...
この中に１人 大人のくせに
Someone in this room
is a grown-up who got in a serious fight with
子供とガチでケンカして
泣かせたヤツがいる
a child and made her cry.
こいつです！
お前だ！
It was him!
It was you!
シロくんを好きになったのを
心配して助言したら
You tried to give her advice to save her from loving Shiro-kun
ケンカになっちゃったの？
どうしてまた…
and ended up getting in a fight?
How did that happen?
シロが私の彼だっつったら
泣いちゃって
She started crying after I said Shiro was my boyfriend.
I didn't say anything because you promised to apologize when she came today...
You're too gullible, Usa-kun.
そんなにマジぼれとは～
I didn't think she liked him that much!
Is that why she cried?
ホントに そうかな？
何か引っ掛かるんだよね
That doesn't seem quite right.
Yeah! There was some other reason, right?!
だよな 別に原因あるよな？
泣いたのは間違いなく 麻弓さんの
驚くほど大人気ない発言のせい
Oh, I can guarantee that she was crying
because your childish tantrum shocked her.
I'm sorry, everyone.
みんな 何かごめん
俺が18歳以上の女性にしか
興味ないばっかりに
This all happened because I'm only interested in women 18 and older.
そこじゃねえよ
むしろ そこブレたら
That's not the problem here.
If that weren't the case, we'd tie you to a pole.
柱に くくりつけます
えッ ありがとう
Really? Thank you!
≪(住子)まあ 明日は
来るかもしれないし➡
Well, she might be back tomorrow.
Let's see how things go.
様子を見てみましょ
結局 昨日も来なかったっすね
She never showed up yesterday, either.
やっぱ シロさんのことが
ショックだったのかな
Was getting rejected by Shiro-san that big of a shock?
でも どこが そんなに
良かったんだろう
I still don't understand what she saw in him.
麻弓さんの言うとおり
宇佐くんの方がいいのにね
Mayumi-san was right. You'd be a better choice.
えッ あッ シロさんと比べたら
高校生だし
Um, I mean, unlike Shiro-san,
you're in high school, and you don't like getting hit,
殴られたら ちゃんと痛がるし
縛り慣れてないし
and you're not used to being tied up,
and you've never been taken by the police, and...
All of that should be common sense, so why am I so happy?
当たり前のことしか
言われてないのに嬉しい俺って…
あれッ あそこにいるのって
千夏ちゃん？
Huh?
Is that Chinatsu-chan?
友達でも待ってるのかな
≪(女の子Ａ)それホント？
Is she waiting for her friends?
Is that true?
(Ｂ)ホントだって
(Ｃ)先生 言ってたもんね
It's true.
The teacher said so.
あからさまに ハブられてる
They're totally shutting her out...
Senpai, do you remember what Mayumi-san said?
先輩 この前の麻弓さんの発言
覚えてます？
｢小学生が色気づきやがって｣
"A little kid shouldn't be thinking about love."
｢ガキは
ガキガキしてりゃいいんだよ｣
"Kids should just be kiddying it up."
ガキガキするって
どうするんだろうね
How do you kiddy it up?
こだわりますね 先輩
あと…
You're really stuck on that part, huh?
And...
《そんなんじゃ ハブられっぞ
バーカ》
Other kids will shut you out if you're like this, idiot!
That was it!
それか！
あわわわ マジで？
Seriously?!
この中に
Someone in this room
rubbed salt in a child's open wound.
小学生のトラウマを
えぐるヤツがいる～
わざとじゃねえもん そういうﾄﾗｳﾏ
持ってるって名札つけといてよ！
It wasn't on purpose!
If they have issues, they should wear nametags saying so!
Hello?
ごめんください
すみません
千夏 おじゃましてませんか？
Excuse me, has Chinatsu been here?
今日は来てませんけど
まだ帰ってきてないんですか？
She didn't come here today.
She's not home yet?
もう暗くなるのに
It's getting dark.
≪(母)行きそうな所
捜してるんですけど
I've been checking all the places she might have gone...
≪(住子)来たら すぐ連絡しますね
≪(母)よろしくお願いします
We'll let you know immediately if she shows up.
Thank you!
≪(ｼﾛ)俺らも 近く捜してこようか
≪(住子)そうね
Should we search nearby?
Yes.
俺 もう少し遠くまで行ってみます
I'll try searching farther away.
お願いね シロくん達は今
小学校の方を…
Please do.
Shiro-kun and everyone else went to check the grade school...
千夏ちゃん
Chinatsu-chan...
思った以上に近くにいたね
You were right under our noses.
≪(住子)お母さんに
連絡しておいたわ➡
I called your mother.
遠くに捜しにいったから
あとで迎えにくるって
She went pretty far away to look for you,
so she'll come pick you up later.
Don't say anything that will make things worse...
と… 友達って難しいよな
F-Friendship can be pretty complicated.
まあ 何だ…
いずれ どうにかなるっつーか
Well, it'll work out eventually.
いなくても なんとかなるっつーか
You don't really even need friends, anyway.
Hollow words...
薄っぺら…
説得力ない
That's not very convincing.
麻弓さん 見るからに学生時代は
充実したタイプだしね
Since Mayumi-san looks like someone who had
lots of friends in school.
｢は｣のボリューム おかしくね？
フンッ
Why was the "had" so much louder?
１年以上 あえて１人で
でもマイペースに過ごしてる
We have a pro loner here who's chosen to spend over a year
現役のプロぼっちも いるしな
living here alone, doing things her way!
家賃３倍
Your rent's tripled.
ごめん マジごめん でも助けて
I'm sorry! I'm really sorry!
But I need your help!
つか 恐ろしい宣言
つぶやかないで～
And don't say scary things like that!
それ ホント？
えッ まあ
Is that true?
I guess...
Aren't you lonely?
≪(千夏)寂しくないの？
えっと その…
Um, well...
楽ではあるかな
≪(千夏)ぼっち先輩は すごいな
It's a lot less stressful.
You're amazing, Loner-senpai.
A smooth sadist!
千夏ちゃんは
もともと友達多そうだし
It seems that you had a lot of friends,
ぼっちっていうより
so you're not really a loner...
ケンカして ハブられたんでしょ？
They're shutting you out because you had a fight.
Payback
Chinatsu-chan, why did you fight with them?
千夏ちゃん ケンカの理由は？
I was having trouble at school, and with my lessons,
最近 勉強とか習い事とか
うまくいかなくて➡
イライラしてて
so I was in a bad mood.
That was when my friends started talking about anime.
≪(千夏)そんなときに友達が
アニメの話をしてきて➡
So I said...
ちょっとだけ きつめに
｢嫌い｣って言ったら➡
I hate it!
a little too harshly, and she started crying.
泣いちゃって➡
Wait!
それを見てた 他の子が
｢ひどい｣って騒ぎ出しちゃって
Everyone else who was watching
said I was a mean person.
No kidding. Who are you anyway?
《≪(男の子)誰だよ
あんなやつクラスにいたか？》
Are you even in this class?
でも 誰にでも好みはあるし
But everyone likes different things,
嫌いなのは仕方ないっていうか…
so it's not my fault I hate it.
その子の話は ちゃんと聞いたの？
Did you listen to what she was saying?
でも もともとアニメ興味ないし
But I never really liked anime.
確かに 好き嫌いはみんな違うし
It's true that everyone likes different things,
そこは仕方ないけど
and you can't help that...
But we all get hurt when a friend says
友達に 自分の好きなものを
簡単に否定されたら
bad things about what we like.
傷つくよ
Oh, so it wasn't anything serious...
アメでも渡して
チャッチャと謝っちゃえよ
Just give them some candy and say you're sorry.
We're not kids. It's not that simple!
子供じゃあるまいし
そんな簡単じゃないもん➡
千夏が教室に入ったり
みんなの近くに行くと➡
Whenever I go into the classroom
and go near all of them,
ピシッて 空気が固まる音がするの
I can actually hear the air freeze.
明日も あの音 聞くかと思うと
When I think about having to go through it again tomorrow,
もう死んじゃいたい
I just wanna die...
The fact that you can say that proves you're just a kid.
そういうこと平気で言うのは
ガキの証拠
最年少が 何てこと言うの
How can someone as young as you say that?
Before you die, would you like some pudding?
死んじゃう前に プリン食べる？
食べる
I would.
Do you want mine?
(シロ)俺のも食べる？
いいの？ 食べる！
Can I? I sure do!
死んじゃいたい なんて思っても
おなかはすくし
You may want to die, but you still get hungry.
好きなもの食べたら
おいしいって思えるし➡
And you still enjoy your favorite food.
体は結構 図太いのよね
Your body is still pretty tough.
≪(千夏)千夏は真剣に悩んで…
I really don't know what to do!
≪(住子)そうよね
それだけ千夏ちゃんは➡
Yes.
Which only shows that you're
強くて まだ力が残ってる
ってことよ
still a very strong person.
戻りたいと思うなら
頑張ってらっしゃい➡
If you want everything to go back to the way it was, you have to work hard.
それでも うまくいかなかったら
そうね➡
If that doesn't work...
Let's see...
バケツプリンでも作ろうかしら
ウフフ
We can make a whole bucket of pudding.
次の週末までに
ピタゴラ装置 完成させとくよ
The Pythagoras device will be done by next weekend.
フィニッシュ
すっごいの作るからさ
I have something great to finish it off.
友達 誘っておいで
Bring your friends along.
Okay.
仲直りできるといいけど
I hope she can make up with her friends.
Oh, I'm still tripling
your rent next month
大丈夫だと思いますよ
I'm sure she'll be fine.
Wait, you
were serious?
だって ハブった子達
何度も振り返ってたから
Wait, you
were serious?
Because the girls who had shut her out
Wait, you
were serious?
kept looking back.
お前 女子小学生よく見てんな
You pay a lot of attention to little girls.
やめて その言い方！
Don't twist my words!
Then, on Saturday...
そして土曜日
住子さん プリン作ってくれる？
Sumiko-san,
will you make pudding?
も もちろんよ
O-Of course.
After you said it'd be fine, she's still all alone!
大丈夫とか大口叩いたのに
お一人様じゃねえかよ
仲良くなれそうじゃない？
黙れ
You should get along with her great.
Quiet!
嬉しいことのお祝いに
おいしいものも アリだよね
It's okay to celebrate with something yummy when good things happen, right?
まあ➡
Absolutely!
もちろんよ！
では シロ＆千夏作
ピタゴラ装置➡
Okay, then!
Time to unveil Shiro and Chinatsu's
Pythagoras Device!
お披露目！
≪(ｼﾛ)流しそうめんﾌｨﾆｯｼｭ
さあ 召し上がれ
And to finish, we have nagashi-somen!
Dig in!
Lame
めっちゃ 滞ってんすけど
The noodles are barely moving.
Lame
I'll go get more water, so hold on.
あッ 今 水くんでくるから
待ってて
わあ すごい もたつき流し
Yeah, it's like a trickle...
尿漏れＣＭを思い出すな
This reminds me of that commercial about wetting yourself.
Bamboo and
water...
劇的に食欲を落とすワード
よく口にしたね！
Way to say something that'll ruin everyone's appetite!
最後のグダグダ仕掛けは
千夏ノータッチだから
I had nothing to do with the failed setup at the end.
ＪＳは 実にＳ！
She's a JS! Just-plain Sadistic!
Had to
resort
to a hose
Had to
resort
to a hose
Had to
resort
to a hose
I bet you your
voice can't hit those
high notes now
I bet you your
voice can't hit those
high notes now
Hey.
ねえ
It can!
ぼっち先輩 楽しい？ 楽しいよね
Are you having fun, Loner-senpai?
You are, right?
楽しいよ
I am.
I knew it!
千夏が友達になってあげよっか
Want me to be your friend?
とりあえず｢ぼっち先輩｣は やめて
Could you stop calling me Loner-senpai first?
≪(住子)千夏ちゃ～ん
Chinatsu-chan.
≪(千夏)わあ～ッ
It's not pudding in a bucket,
バケツプリンじゃないけど
お味は いかが？
but does it taste good?
Delicious!
≪(女の子達)おいしい！
あれから全然来なくなったっすね
She hasn't been back ever since.
She's probably busy playing with her friends.
友達と遊ぶので
忙しいんじゃない？
俺を好きって言ったのも
逃避の一種だから➡
She only said she was in love with me as a way to escape.
社会の はみ出し者でも
楽しく生きてて➡
She did say she felt better after seeing that
見てて楽になる って言ってたし
an outcast like me could still have fun.
Ｓっすね
She is sadistic.
寂しいですか？
子供は それでいいんだって
Do you miss her?
That's how kids should be.
必要なときに大人を頼って
They can rely on grown-ups when they need to,
切り捨てて 踏んで
縛っていってくれれば
then abandon them and stomp on them!
I don't want that.
俺は やですよ
≪(住子)宇佐くん シロくん
ごはんよ
Usa-kun, Shiro-kun, it's time for dinner.
は～い
Okay!
うまそう トンカツ？
This looks good!
Are those pork cutlets?
住子さん
Sumiko-san...
別に俺 落ち込んでないよ
I'm not feeling sad or anything.
ウフフ あらそう？
Oh? Really now?
Oh.
<あッ これって…>
This is the spineless chicken's favorite: boneless chicken!
<チキンカスの好きな
チキンカツだ>
A
shi
We'll
all
stay
pitiful
tomorrow
ta
mo
bo
ku
ra
wa
mi
n
na
ka
wa
i
so
u
A
shi
Preview
Uh-oh! They say there's a molester in the area!
最近 この辺にチカンが出るって
(彩花)地獄に落ちればいい
That's disgusting! He deserves to burn in hell!
(シロ)彩花ちゃんは
自力で落とすでしょ
You could send him to hell yourself.
What? I have no idea what you mean.
無傷じゃかえさないけど
２人はともかく先輩が心配
He wouldn't get away unscathed, for sure.
I'm more worried about Senpai than you two!
(ｼﾛ)ﾁｶﾝなんてﾍﾀﾚの最低男
Molesters are the lowest kind of scum there is!
(彩花)心が折れるｾﾘﾌぶつければ
撃退できるよ
If you keep throwing insults, you can usually wear them down.
Really?!
｢この粗チン野郎｣
(彩花)｢ちっちゃくて見えない｣
Like, "Nice peashooter!"
"Wow, it's so small that I can't even see it!"
Yes! Let's have Senpai practice saying those things!
先輩にそういうｾﾘﾌの練習を！
(彩花)言わせて どうするつもり？
Why do you want Rit-chan to say those things?
シロだけじゃなく
貴様もＭだったか
So you're a masochist like Shiro.
Episode Seven
We Recommend
Uh, that's not what I meant.
最低
誤解ですってば！
You're disgusting.
You've got it all wrong!